
<text>
<section eDate="6 July 11" ><![CDATA[Happy Summer! Six lovely months in San Francisco passed like a flash with new work for Lucky NYC, Goodby Silverstein, Leroy and Clarkson, EVB, and Social Control.]]>
</section>
<section eDate="26 January 11" ><![CDATA[Back in San Francisco and it feels comfy like a home should. Lately been keeping busy with local EVB and Little Red Robot, but am available for future bookings both here and away. Yay for the Best Coast!]]>
</section>
<section eDate="21 November 10" ><![CDATA[Returning to the US soon, but not yet to California. I just signed on to work onsite at The Mill in NYC for the month of December. See you in New York?]]>
</section>
<section eDate="3 November 10" ><![CDATA[Just found out that Current Green won a Merit Award and will be featured in the How Magazine 2011 Interactive Design Annual. I am super excited!]]>
</section>
<section eDate="28 October 10" ><![CDATA[Arriving back to the USA on November 29, return is set!  See you back in California soon!]]>
</section>
<section eDate="20 September 10" ><![CDATA[My work is to be included in the upcoming ArtCrank poster show in San Francisco! I will be living in Berlin, Germany from Sept-Nov and sadly missing the excitement back home. Perhaps you can be there instead? www.artcrankpostershow.com/san-francisco]]>
</section>
<section eDate="06 July 10" ><![CDATA[Leaving for a week in Mexico City. In the meantime, enjoy some new updated boards and contact me if you would like to work together in mid-July!]]>
</section>
<section eDate="28 March 10" ><![CDATA[Busy couple months doing work for Buck, BNS NY, Social Control, Roger, The Mill, The History Channel and others.  Viva la freelance! A few new boards to show, a few coming soon. PLUS see .mov at vimeo.com/calcium75 and personal work at meghantosh.com]]>
</section>
<section eDate="09 November 09" ><![CDATA[NEW REEL IS UP, visions and revisions be damned!  Lately? I edited four trailers to     support www.storiesofhealth.org and I have       been designing and letterpressing a series of greeting cards which will be available soon.]]>
</section>
<section eDate="18 September 09" ><![CDATA[Excitement! Two weeks notice and heartfelt goodbye to Current TV, I will soon be back to the freewheeling, freelancing lifestyle! I am accepting bookings for October and a new reel is forthcoming - I promise.  Lots of great new work to show!]]>
</section>
<section eDate="08 February 09" ><![CDATA[On February 28th I will be competing live in motion design at Cut and Paste.  I have never been in a designer death match -- wish me luck! Or better yet, get tix for the SF match at cutandpaste.com]]>
</section>
<section eDate="13 October 08" ><![CDATA[Updates!  New design I have done in the last couple months for Stardust, Roger, Digital Kitchen and Grand Jetee.  Reel update soon.]]>
</section>
<section eDate="19 May 08" ><![CDATA[I have landed at Current TV in a long term freelance graphic design position since mid-april.  Love it here, but still keeping up with the night and weekend freelance board design jobs.]]>
</section>
<section eDate="23 March 08" ><![CDATA[UPDATES!  So much new work to see below.            It looks like San Francisco wins.  You can find me there or on the internet.]]>
</section>
<section eDate="2 March 08" ><![CDATA[BIG CHANGES! Finally left LA. My stuff is in a storage cube, and I will be in either San Francsico, Portland, or Minneapolis for the next couple months. I am actively looking for additional remote freelance design and animation work. Contact me!]]>
</section>
<section eDate="29 February 08" ><![CDATA[ Spent a nice two months at Yu and Co in Hollywood this January and February.  Lots of new work to add soon.  ]]>
</section>
<section eDate="24 December 07" ><![CDATA[Back in the USA!]]>
</section>
<section eDate="1 November 07" ><![CDATA[Just started another stint with the wonderful folks at Logan.  I will be here until mid-December and then heading to Tokyo for two weeks. It is good to be back in Venice Beach.]]>
</section>
<section eDate="12 October 07" ><![CDATA[Back from South America!  Contemporary design in Buenos Aires and pre-columbian Peruvian textile design have me totally inspired.  After getting sick I left early to make use of all this inspiration in the comfort of LA with my computer, my boy, and my cats.]]>
</section>

<section eDate="17 September 07" ><![CDATA[Here is the new site design!  There will be many improvements in the next week, including a new cut of my reel with a matching intro and an update to my resume.  In the meantime, check the other stuff out...]]>
</section>

<section eDate="16 September 07" ><![CDATA[It is my last week of several lovely weeks at Framework and I am off to Peru.  I return Oct 17!]]>
</section>

<section eDate="15 September 07" ><![CDATA[I just registered www.mybicyclefriend.com to celebrate all things bicycle.  I love riding my bike to work and want to encourage everyone to do so! Look for some cool design, animation, and forums in the coming weeks.]]>
</section>



</text>